DANIEL FANELLI

700 Bogue Road Apt 5, Yuba City, CA 95991 | (H) (407)615-0533 | (C) 4076150533 | daniel.r.fanellijr@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-fanelli-4b186232/ Personal: http://www.danielfanelli.com

Professional Summary

A strongly driven professional who is customer-oriented, possessing advanced technical skills and extensive experience in medical billing and database management.

Skills

- Centricity
- Microsoft SQL Server
- Data Management
- Data Analysis
- Active Directory
- Troubleshooting
- HIPAA
- Medical Billing
- ICD 10 Diagnosis Codes
- CPT Procedure Codes
- Call Center/Customer Service
- Accounts Receivable
- Revenue Cycle
- Microsoft Office
- Pivot Tables

- Microsoft Server 2013
- Accounts Receivable
- Revenue Cycle
- Microsoft Office
- Pivot Tables
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- C#
- Search Engine Optimization
- Audio/Video Production
- HTMI
- Responsive Web Design
- Adobe Creative Suite

Certifications

- Full Stack Web Development Certification
- HFMA CRCR
- CompTIA A+
- CompTIA Net+

Work History

Account Resolution Specialist

05/2016 to 03/2017

Healthcare Excellence Institute - Phoenix, Arizona, United States

- Reduced outstanding AR patient and insurance balances.
- •Successfully Became HFMA CRCR Certified in October 2016.
- Met and exceeded expectations in regular performance reviews individually and organizationally.
- Followed up on the processing of claims with insurance and ensured all accounts were resolved in a timely manner.

Data Manager

04/2014 to 09/2015

CoopDIGITy, Inc - Marysville, California, United States

- Collected and loaded monthly data from distributors.
- Used SQL Server Management 2014 and Microsoft Office 2010 to carry out daily tasks related to data management.
- Resolved client support requests including account set up/permissions, and data validation/reporting issues.

Lead Medical Biller

05/2009 to 04/2014

West Coast Billing Solutions - Yuba City, CA

- Provided technical support assistance as needed such as data clean up, virus scans, tune ups, computer network set up, printing issues, and diagnostic services.
- Performed medical billing tasks including patient account support, posting charges and payments.
- Reduced outstanding AR patient and insurance balances.

Owner/Videographer

01/2007 to 12/2010

A Majestic Moment Digital Studios - Orlando, Florida, United States

- Designed and updated company website including search engine optimization.
- Presented and provided video services for weddings and special events.
- Supervised all aspects of live and post production from planning to completion of video.

Education

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: Web Development Coder Camps - Scottsdale, AZ

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#, ASP.NET, SQL, Angular, Responsive Design
 Pending completion of fitness app for tracking workout goals.

Bachelor of Arts: Radio Television Production

- University of Central Florida Orlando, FL

 Admitted into University of Central Florida with 9 letters of recommendations in 1997.

 Accepted to Nicholson School of Communications in 2008 with a 3.4 GPA.

 Completed several three internships at Cox Media and AMFM, Inc.

2001